<Root>
	<HoneycombComposite>
		<name>
			Honeycomb Composite Plating
		</name>
		<desc>
			A strong lightweight panel with extremely low thermal conductivity, and very effective force and vibration absorption capabilities.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</HoneycombComposite>
	<CrystalLens>
		<name>
			Refractive Lens
		</name>
		<desc>
			A lens with the ability to refract several kinds of energy and waves.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</CrystalLens>
	<HullPlating>
		<name>
			Hull Plating
		</name>
		<desc>
			Heavy armor for vehicles.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</HullPlating>
	<Sealant>
		<name>
			Sealant
		</name>
		<desc>
			A thick goo useful for impregnating other materials to induce impermeability.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Sealant>
	<SealFabric>
		<name>
			Sealed Fabric
		</name>
		<desc>
			Fabric woven together and thoroughly saturated with sealing compounds.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SealFabric>
	<SealedSuit>
		<name>
			Electrochemical Suit
		</name>
		<desc>
			A suit made of molecularly impenetrable fabric.
			Stops almost all electrical and chemical penetration, but does little against radiation or thermal hazards.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SealedSuit>
	<RebreatherV2>
		<name>
			Liquid Breathing System
		</name>
		<desc>
			A breathing apparatus that uses an oxygen-saturated perfluorocarbon liquid instead of air.
			Allows for respiration at extreme depths and pressures without risk of barotrauma or toxicity from gas mixtures.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</RebreatherV2>
	<VENT_CRYSTAL>
		<name>
			Azurite
		</name>
		<desc>
			A luminous gemstone with exquisite optical properties and electromagnetic conductivity.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Found exclusively around certain thermal vents, these exotic crystals, despite having a similar gross molecular structure to common quartz, have electron distributions more commonly seen in metallic elements.
			
			This material can only form under very particular circumstances, specifically where superheated, mineral-rich water is injected into cold water, in the absence of dense flora which would absorb, or fast currents which would disperse the minerals before they can recrystallize. During this recrystallization process, many of the material's electrons are temporarily trapped within the crystal structure in a higher energy state.
			
			The light emitted by these deposits originates from those electrons the crystal structure dropping back into the ground state, releasing a photon in the process. While they remain energized, these electrons imbue the crystal structure with both high electrical and magnetic conductivity, allowing it to channel and reflect fields of the same.
			
			This arrangement also makes the crystal fairly unstable; Careless handling can result in violent fracturing, which destroys the aforementioned structure and releases a large quantity of energy.
		</pda>
	</VENT_CRYSTAL>
	<PLATINUM>
		<name>
			Platinum
		</name>
		<desc>
			A dense, valuable, rare metal with extreme resistance to corrosion. In addition to being useful for creating alloys, it is also useful as a chemical catalyst with organic compounds.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Rarer and more valuable even than gold, platinum is a transition metal whose chief property is its extremely low chemical reactivity. This makes it all but impervious to corrosion, and allows it to mediate many chemical reactions without being consumed itself. In particular it is well-suited to rearranging the components of organic molecules.
		</pda>
	</PLATINUM>
	<PRESSURE_CRYSTALS>
		<name>
			Abyssoclase
		</name>
		<desc>
			Small, dense crystals formed under extreme pressure, with trace amounts of exotic elements such as Tellurium.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			In the deepest layers of the open ocean, where mineral-rich water expelled from thermal vents collects due to its greater density relative to ordinary seawater, the extreme pressure can force these minerals back out of solution.
			
			Abyssoclase is one such mineral, formed when a small seed crystal - possibly quartz, diamond, or sulfur - is coated with successive layers of silcia deposits rich in Tellurium and other rare elements.
			
			These deposits, due to the nature of the environment in which they form, are extremely dense, hard, and resistant to compressive forces. If integrated into another substrate, they can massively increase that material's mechanical strength.
		</pda>
	</PRESSURE_CRYSTALS>
	<PHASE_CRYSTAL>
		<name>
			Avolite
		</name>
		<desc>
			An integral part of a phase gate, allowing for the high-level manipulation of space and time.
			These crystals are not fully understood, but are known to only form in deep space.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</PHASE_CRYSTAL>
	<IRIDIUM>
		<name>
			Iridium
		</name>
		<desc>
			An exotic 
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</IRIDIUM>
	<ALKALI_PLANT>
		<name>
			Alkali Vines
		</name>
		<desc>
			A rare plant only found in certain ecological niches with high mineral content and low exposure to light.
			
			This plant is comprised of a fibrous tube filled with a strongly alkaline gel. The primary purpose of this may be to deter creatures from eating the stems, or it may help the conduction of the plant's biochemical processes.
			
			Assessment: Inedible but possibly useful from a chemistry standpoint
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</ALKALI_PLANT>
	<SeamothVoidStealth>
		<name>
			Acoustic Suppression Module
		</name>
		<desc>
			Greatly reduces the detectability of basic seamoth systems to passive listeners.
			Will not affect active echolocators, or creatures at close range.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeamothVoidStealth>
	<enum>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</enum>
</Root>