<Root>
	<HoneycombComposite>
		<name>
			Honeycomb Composite Plating
		</name>
		<desc>
			A strong lightweight panel with extremely low thermal conductivity, and very effective force and vibration absorption capabilities.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</HoneycombComposite>
	<CrystalLens>
		<name>
			Refractive Lens
		</name>
		<desc>
			A lens with the ability to refract several kinds of energy and waves.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</CrystalLens>
	<HullPlating>
		<name>
			Hull Plating
		</name>
		<desc>
			Heavy armor for vehicles.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</HullPlating>
	<VENT_CRYSTAL>
		<name>
			Azurite
		</name>
		<desc>
			A luminous gemstone with exquisite optical properties and electromagnetic conductivity.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Found exclusively around certain thermal vents, these exotic crystals, despite having a similar molecular structure to common quartz, have electron distributions more commonly seen in metallic elements.
			
			The light emitted by these deposits originates from the slow decomposition of chemical compounds loosely bound in its silica substrate. This arrangement is fairly unstable, which has two main effects:
			-This material can only form under very particular circumstances, specifically where superheated, mineral-rich water is injected into cold water, in the absence of dense flora which would absorb the minerals before they can recrystallize.
			-Careless handling of these crystals can result in violent fracturing, which destroys their normal crystal structure and releases a large quantity of energy.
			
			This free movement and 
		</pda>
	</VENT_CRYSTAL>
	<PLATINUM>
		<name>
			Platinum
		</name>
		<desc>
			A dense, valuable, rare metal with extreme resistance to corrosion. In addition to being useful for creating alloys, it is also useful as a chemical catalyst with organic compounds.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</PLATINUM>
	<PRESSURE_CRYSTALS>
		<name>
			Abyssoclase
		</name>
		<desc>
			Small, dense crystals formed under extreme pressure, with trace amounts of exotic elements such as Tellurium.
			Potentially able to be alloyed into other materials for increased compressive strength.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</PRESSURE_CRYSTALS>
	<PHASE_CRYSTAL>
		<name>
			Avolite
		</name>
		<desc>
			An integral part of a phase gate, allowing for the high-level manipulation of space and time.
			These crystals are not fully understood, but are known to only form in deep space.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</PHASE_CRYSTAL>
	<IRIDIUM>
		<name>
			Iridium
		</name>
		<desc>
			An exotic 
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</IRIDIUM>
	<enum>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</enum>
</Root>