<Root>
	<HoneycombComposite>
		<name>
			Honeycomb Composite Plating
		</name>
		<desc>
			A strong lightweight panel with extremely low thermal conductivity, and very effective force and vibration absorption capabilities.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</HoneycombComposite>
	<DenseAzurite>
		<name>
			Shaped Azurite
		</name>
		<desc>
			A more densely packed and energetically useful form of Azurite.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</DenseAzurite>
	<CrystalLens>
		<name>
			Refractive Lens
		</name>
		<desc>
			A lens with the ability to refract several kinds of energy and waves.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</CrystalLens>
	<HullPlating>
		<name>
			Hull Plating
		</name>
		<desc>
			Heavy armor for vehicles.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</HullPlating>
	<Sealant>
		<name>
			Sealant
		</name>
		<desc>
			A thick goo useful for impregnating other materials to induce impermeability.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Sealant>
	<HeatSealant>
		<name>
			Heat-sealed Fabric
		</name>
		<desc>
			An advanced textile designed to not just insulate materials against chemical attack, but thermally isolate them as well.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</HeatSealant>
	<SealFabric>
		<name>
			Sealed Fabric
		</name>
		<desc>
			Fabric woven together and thoroughly saturated with sealing compounds.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SealFabric>
	<Chlorine>
		<name>
			Chlorine
		</name>
		<desc>
			Cl. A highly poisonous gas which dissolves easily in water. Good for killing microorganisms.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Chlorine>
	<Luminol>
		<name>
			Luminol
		</name>
		<desc>
			C8H7N3O2. A luminous fluid, colorless in small amounts and pale blue in large quantities.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Luminol>
	<SmartPolymer>
		<name>
			Smart Polymer
		</name>
		<desc>
			A flexible plastic material that remembers its original shape and returns to it when stress is released.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SmartPolymer>
	<WeakAcid>
		<name>
			Carboxylic Acid
		</name>
		<desc>
			CH3(CH2)xCOOH. A dilute organic acid, suitable for use in basic electronics.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</WeakAcid>
	<SulfurAcid>
		<name>
			Sulfuric Acid
		</name>
		<desc>
			H2SO4. A concentrated inorganic acid. Useful to catalyze chemical reactions.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SulfurAcid>
	<Motor>
		<name>
			Electric Motor
		</name>
		<desc>
			A midsize motor, capable of generating sufficient power to move sizeable machinery, pump fluids, or drive propulsion systems.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Motor>
	<TreaderEnzymes>
		<name>
			Digestive Enzymes
		</name>
		<desc>
			Trace chemicals extracted from the digestive output of large animals.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</TreaderEnzymes>
	<BioEnzymes>
		<name>
			Lysing Enzymes
		</name>
		<desc>
			Organic chemicals suitable for breaking down biological matter into simpler chemicals.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</BioEnzymes>
	<LathingDrone>
		<name>
			Nanolathing Drone
		</name>
		<desc>
			A self-propelled drone equipped with a construction beam for constructing large objects from raw materials, similar to robotic builder tools.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</LathingDrone>
	<KelpEnzymes>
		<name>
			Microbiotic Gel
		</name>
		<desc>
			A compound harvested from inside deepvine leaves, designed to support bacterial growth and metabolism. Will enhance the efficiency of biochemical processing.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</KelpEnzymes>
	<BacterialSample>
		<name>
			Bacterial Samples
		</name>
		<desc>
			A quantity of bacteria, highly specialized for recombining organic compounds.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</BacterialSample>
	<FuelTankWall>
		<name>
			Tank Wall
		</name>
		<desc>
			A high-tech blend of materials with the right balance of elasticity and strength to contain reactive and dangerous rocket fuel.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</FuelTankWall>
	<RocketFuel>
		<name>
			Neptune Rocket Fuel
		</name>
		<desc>
			A chemical mixture capable of releasing extreme amounts of energy on demand.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</RocketFuel>
	<BrokenT2Battery>
		<name>
			Damaged Azurite Battery
		</name>
		<desc>
			A damaged azurite battery. Can be restored to full functionality with some component replacements, at a reduced cost compared to crafting a fresh battery.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</BrokenT2Battery>
	<AmoeboidSample>
		<name>
			Amoeboid Samples
		</name>
		<desc>
			Strands of colonial bacteria, evolved to leach minerals from rock.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</AmoeboidSample>
	<TraceMetals>
		<name>
			Rare Elements
		</name>
		<desc>
			Trace quantities of rare metal and semimetal elements, used in advanced fabrication.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</TraceMetals>
	<GeyserMinerals>
		<name>
			Volcanic Traces
		</name>
		<desc>
			Small quantities of igneous materials, filtered from geyser output.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</GeyserMinerals>
	<WeakEnzyme42>
		<name>
			Enzyme 42 Traces
		</name>
		<desc>
			A small amount of enzyme 42, but too impure and degraded to properly cure Kharaa infection.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</WeakEnzyme42>
	<Nanocarbon>
		<name>
			Nanocarbon
		</name>
		<desc>
			Carbon nanotubes, woven together into sheets which are then heat-fused together. An advanced industrial product not producible by standard fabrication technology.
			
			&lt;b&gt;Will break down when submerged in water.&lt;/b&gt;
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Nanocarbon>
	<breathfluid>
		<name>
			Breathing Fluid
		</name>
		<desc>
			CFx•Oy. A nontoxic solvent saturated with oxygen, suitable for liquid-based respiration.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</breathfluid>
	<SealedSuit>
		<name>
			Electrochemical Suit
		</name>
		<desc>
			A suit made of molecularly impenetrable fabric.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			An upgrade for the basic AEP suit, the electrochemical suit is woven from a dense, chemically-sealed mesh of treated fibers, and confers great resistance against both electrical and chemical hazards, allowing for survival in toxic or highly charged environments.
			
			Disclaimer: Stops almost all electrical and chemical penetration, but does little against radiation or thermal hazards. Not rated for acid exposure.
		</pda>
	</SealedSuit>
	<SealedGloves>
		<name>
			Electrochemical Gloves
		</name>
		<desc>
			Because wearing a protective suit but grabbing things with your bare hands would work about as well as punching out a reaper.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SealedGloves>
	<RebreatherV2>
		<name>
			Recirculation Mask
		</name>
		<desc>
			A motorized face mask equipped with the ability to actively pump a breathing medium from storage and either recirculate it back to the tank or force waste gas out against very high pressures.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			At depths where the rebreather can no longer suffice, causing oxygen consumption to increase to ever more unmanageable levels, the recirculation mask becomes a highly valuable piece of survival equipment. Motorized gas delivery and exhaust mechanisms overcome these pressures and eliminate most of the wasted source gas, greatly extending the maximum practical duration of a dive.
			
			A requirement for liquid breathing hardware to function.
		</pda>
	</RebreatherV2>
	<LiquidTank>
		<name>
			Liquid Breathing System
		</name>
		<desc>
			A breathing apparatus that uses an oxygen-saturated perfluorocarbon liquid instead of air.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			At great depths, the extreme water pressure makes freediving impossible with normal respiratory mechanisms. The liquid breathing system solves that limitation, and allows for respiration at extreme depths and pressures without risk of barotrauma or toxicity from gas mixtures.
			
			Note:
			- Requires a compatible facemask to function
			- Contains a main tank and a small (150 second) supply tank, only the latter of which is able to be directly drawn upon during diving
			- Main tank can only refill the supply tank when in a powered space
			- Consumes breathing fluid to refill the main tank, and requires a compatible fluid pump module installed in a seabase to do so
		</pda>
	</LiquidTank>
	<CurativeBandage>
		<name>
			Nanowrap Bandages
		</name>
		<desc>
			A highly sophisticated wound dressing, capable of restoring far more health than a basic first aid kit, staunching any blood loss, and alleviating all symptoms of poisoning or other ongoing harming effects.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</CurativeBandage>
	<KharaaTreatment>
		<name>
			Kharaa Symptom Alleviation Canister
		</name>
		<desc>
			Provides temporary relief from Kharaa symptoms that reduce pulmonary efficiency, especially when using liquid respiration media. Does not lose effectiveness with use, but will do nothing to combat the infection.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</KharaaTreatment>
	<VENT_CRYSTAL>
		<name>
			Azurite
		</name>
		<desc>
			Cu3(CO3)2(OH)2•8-. A luminous gemstone with exquisite optical properties and electromagnetic conductivity.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Found exclusively around certain thermal vents, these exotic crystals, despite having a similar gross molecular structure to common quartz, have electron distributions more commonly seen in metallic elements.
			
			This material can only form under very particular circumstances, specifically where superheated, mineral-rich water is injected into cold water, in the absence of dense flora which would absorb, or fast currents which would disperse, the minerals before they can recrystallize. During this recrystallization process, many of the material's electrons are temporarily trapped within the crystal structure in a higher energy state.
			
			The light emitted by these deposits originates from those electrons the crystal structure dropping back into the ground state, releasing a photon in the process. While they remain energized, these electrons imbue the crystal structure with both high electrical and magnetic conductivity, allowing it to channel and reflect fields of the same.
			
			This arrangement also makes the crystal fairly unstable; Careless handling can result in violent fracturing, which destroys the aforementioned structure and releases a large quantity of energy.
		</pda>
		<header>
			azurite
		</header>
	</VENT_CRYSTAL>
	<PLATINUM>
		<name>
			Platinum
		</name>
		<desc>
			Pt. A dense, valuable, rare metal with extreme resistance to corrosion. In addition to being useful for creating alloys, it is also useful as a chemical catalyst with organic compounds.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Rarer and more valuable even than gold, platinum is a transition metal whose chief property is its extremely low chemical reactivity. This makes it all but impervious to corrosion, and allows it to mediate many chemical reactions without being consumed itself. In particular it is well-suited to rearranging the components of organic molecules.
			
			The extreme rarity of this metal can be partly attributed to its high density; during planetary formation and meteoric bombardment, it sinks to the core, leaving only traces in the crust. What little is left further settles to the lowest layers of the sediment, only becoming available via excavation or other disturbances to said sediment.
		</pda>
		<header>
			platinum
		</header>
	</PLATINUM>
	<PRESSURE_CRYSTALS>
		<name>
			Abyssoclase
		</name>
		<desc>
			Small, dense crystals formed under extreme pressure, with trace amounts of exotic elements such as Tellurium.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			In the deepest layers of the open ocean, where mineral-rich water collects due to its greater density relative to ordinary seawater, the extreme pressure can force these minerals back out of solution.
			
			Abyssoclase is one such mineral, formed when a small seed crystal - possibly quartz, diamond, or sulfur - is coated with successive layers of silcia deposits rich in Tellurium and other rare elements.
			
			These deposits, due to the nature of the environment in which they form, are extremely dense, hard, and resistant to compressive forces. If integrated into another substrate, they can massively increase that material's mechanical strength.
		</pda>
		<header>
			voidspike
		</header>
	</PRESSURE_CRYSTALS>
	<PHASE_CRYSTAL>
		<name>
			Avolite
		</name>
		<desc>
			An integral part of ship drives and phase gates. These crystals are not fully understood, but are known to only form in deep space.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Avolite is an extremely rare crystal with extraordinary physical properties, the underlying mechanisms of which are very poorly understood, to the point where in eras past its properties would have been ascribed to theological origins and perhaps even formed the basis of primitive religions.
			
			This mineral demonstrates behavior analogous to the piezoelectric effect, except on a far larger scale, dragging spacetime itself as it warps when subjected to electromagnetic fields.
			
			This ability to manipulate space and time makes these crystals an integral part of both interstellar propulsion systems and phase gates, and as a result Avolite is one of the most prized minerals in existence.
		</pda>
		<header>
			avolite
		</header>
	</PHASE_CRYSTAL>
	<IRIDIUM>
		<name>
			Iridium
		</name>
		<desc>
			Ir. An exotic and dense metal not typically found in most geologic strata.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Iridium is not typically present in detectable quantities in planetary crusts, instead often only being found in meteorite deposits. High concentrations of this rare and dense metal are often indicators that the area is geologically linked with such an impactor.
		</pda>
		<header>
			iridium
		</header>
	</IRIDIUM>
	<ALKALI_PLANT>
		<name>
			Alkali Vines
		</name>
		<desc>
			A plant with alkaline gel filling its structure.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			This plant is fairly rare, found only in certain ecological niches with high mineral content and low exposure to light.
			
			The main body of the plant is comprised of a fibrous tube filled with a strongly alkaline gel. The primary purpose of this may be to deter creatures from eating the stems, or it may help the conduction of the plant's biochemical processes.
			
			This plant possesses an unusual ability to detect disturbances in the water nearby, and will retract into the seabed for protection when approached by potential predators. Avoiding such detection will be necessary to allow samples to be taken.
			
			Assessment: Inedible but possibly useful from a chemistry standpoint, if its defenses can be circumvented
		</pda>
		<header>
			AlkaliVines
		</header>
	</ALKALI_PLANT>
	<VENT_KELP>
		<name>
			Deepvine
		</name>
		<desc>
			A tall deepwater plant, filling a similar role to creepvine in its local ecosystem.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Deepvine differs substantially in appearance from its shallow-water counterpart, but genetic analysis reveals a close relationship. Like creepvine, it acts as both food and shelter for the local population of small fauna, supporting an ecosystem more rich in biomass than would typically be possible at this depth.
			
			Unlike normal creepvine, however, deepvine has evolved to depend on chemosynthesis based on minerals ejected by nearby geothermal activity in the lieu of sunlight. This is accomplished by the leaves harboring extensive colonies of several species of bacteria which can perform biochemical reactions at far greater rate and efficiency than would be possible without them.
			
			Assessment: Inedibly toxic but the bacteria may be repurposed to improve the efficacy of chemical reactions
		</pda>
		<header>
			DeepVine
		</header>
	</VENT_KELP>
	<HEALING_FLOWER>
		<name>
			Salve Bush
		</name>
		<desc>
			A plant with leaves possessing curative properties for physical, thermal, and chemical wounds.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Oils on the leaves of this plant act as natural analgesics, antiseptics, and anti-inflammatories, making them extremely potent as a component in bandages and wound dressings, but unsuitable for consumption.
			
			Assessment: Critical component of advanced healing equipment
		</pda>
		<header>
			SalveBush
		</header>
	</HEALING_FLOWER>
	<MOUNTAIN_GLOW>
		<name>
			Pyropod Pitcher
		</name>
		<desc>
			Plant pods containing a complex mix of biological compounds, encased in a tough fibrous shell capable of withstanding high temperatures.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Like several other apparent species on 4546B, pyropods are in fact two distinct organisms, but - unusually for species encountered thus far - this relationship is not in fact symbiotic, but instead unquestionably parasitic. The host plant's most notable characteristic is the hard vaselike structure it forms around itself; this is perhaps an attempt at armoring itself against the parasite, though it is quite ineffective if this is in fact its purpose.
			
			The other plant takes the form of several glowing pods, each containing a noxious soup of chemicals. When attached to the host plant, the parasite consumes its leaves and injects these compounds into the host plant, triggering rapid chemical breakdown of its internal structures into nutrients which the parasite can then consume. The resultant reaction heats the interior of the base to the point of measurably raising the surrounding water temperature.
			
			Assessment: Slightly dangerous but useful in crafting processes
		</pda>
		<header>
			MountainGlow
		</header>
	</MOUNTAIN_GLOW>
	<SANCTUARY_PLANT>
		<name>
			Eye Flame
		</name>
		<desc>
			The glowing core harvested from an eye flame. Generates a voltage when subjected to mechanical, thermal, or chemical stimulation.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Only encountered in a small ecological niche in a remote corner of the crash zone, this floral species may have once been far more abundant; the remaining area where these plants are found may only be a small remnant of what was once a larger region before the crash, but has since been replaced with a sandy wasteland.
			
			The main body of the plant consists of two layered bowls of upwards-facing violet petals, set atop a flat ring of wide, firm, waxy leaves. While these leaves exhibit some luminescence and texture, they are not the most remarkable aspect of this species.
			
			At the center of the organism, lies a soft sac of electrochemically active  - and extraordinarily luminescent - tissue. When subjected to thermal, mechanical, or chemical stimulation, such as flexion or a change in ambient pH, the cells in this organ start to generate an electrical potential, which over the entire body of the organ can amount to a significant voltage. The utility of this mechanism is unknown, but it may serve some role in the plant's reproductive lifecycle, perhaps signaling to the embedded seeds to begin the development process.
			
			Assessment: Applications in fabrication of electrically active materials
		</pda>
		<header>
			SanctuaryPlant
		</header>
	</SANCTUARY_PLANT>
	<TREE_BACTERIA>
		<name>
			Bacterial Colony
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			The cave system inside the fossilized tree creates a sheltered environment where unique lifeforms can thrive. One of the most visible of these takes the form of large, dome-shaped colonies of bacteria which leach minerals from the cave walls to power their metabolism.
			
			Assessment: Further study may yield insights into manipulation of biochemical reactions
		</pda>
	</TREE_BACTERIA>
	<GEYSER_CORAL>
		<name>
			Geyser Coral
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			This coral species filters trace minerals from volcanic emissions, specifically the superheated, turbulent, mineral-rich effluent from geyser eruptions. This coral is extremely sensitive to the local conditions, and is unlikely to be able to survive anywhere outside of this cave system. Furthermore, its presence indicates such a volcanic feature deeper in the cave network.
			
			Assessment: Further study will enable mechanical imitation of a similar filtration process
		</pda>
	</GEYSER_CORAL>
	<DeepStalker>
		<name>
			Abyssal Stalker
		</name>
		<desc>
			A deep-sea relative of the common stalker.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			A relative of the stalkers found in shallow creepvine forests, this species has adapted to the low-light conditions of its environment, using the darkness for camouflage in lieu of hiding in dense foliage.
			
			One trait that has been preserved or even amplified, however, is the Stalker's attraction to metallic materials; Abyssal Stalkers will congregate around sources of such materials, and will aggressively defend them from potential rivals.
			
			The purpose of the bioluminescent features on the stalker may be to aid this intimidation, or they may be designed to attract small prey fish.
		</pda>
		<header>
			deepstalker
		</header>
	</DeepStalker>
	<VoidSpikeLevi>
		<name>
			 Galvanic Leviathan
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
		<header>
			voidlevi
		</header>
	</VoidSpikeLevi>
	<SeamothVoidStealth>
		<name>
			Acoustic Suppression Module
		</name>
		<desc>
			Greatly reduces the detectability of basic seamoth systems to passive listeners.
			Will not affect active echolocators, or creatures at close range.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeamothVoidStealth>
	<SeamothPowerSeal>
		<name>
			Electrical Sealant Module
		</name>
		<desc>
			Applies an insulating coating to the seamoth exterior, significantly reducing the power loss when in conductive environments.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeamothPowerSeal>
	<SeaMothSpeed>
		<name>
			Seamoth Propulsion Module
		</name>
		<desc>
			An upgrade for the seamoth propulsor that increases base speed and allows for short bursts of even higher speed.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeaMothSpeed>
	<SeamothHeatSinkModule>
		<name>
			Seamoth Heat Sink Module
		</name>
		<desc>
			Allows the seamoth to dump large quantities of heat quickly, helping it survive in extremely hot environments. Derived from spacecraft technology.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeamothHeatSinkModule>
	<SeamothHeatSink>
		<name>
			Seamoth Heat Sink
		</name>
		<desc>
			A consumable item for the heat sink module to operate.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeamothHeatSink>
	<t2battery>
		<name>
			Azurite Battery
		</name>
		<desc>
			A better battery, with significantly greater storage density. Its material construction precludes being adapted into a vehicular power cell.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</t2battery>
	<CyclopsHeat>
		<name>
			Cyclops Heat Dissipation Module
		</name>
		<desc>
			Provides the ability for the cyclops to shed excess heat in superheated environments, preventing serious overheating and fire.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</CyclopsHeat>
	<redkey>
		<name>
			Red Tablet
		</name>
		<desc>
			Ancient alien tablet with a red symbol.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			This device is dominated by an illuminated red symbol resembling a capital 'R'.
			
			Like other similar tablets, it presumably grants access to restricted spaces, with the special nature of this tablet - both its rarity and its seeming authority - probably indicating a similarly exclusive location, perhaps one only normally granting access to a select few.
		</pda>
		<category>
			DownloadedData/Precursor/Scan
		</category>
	</redkey>
	<whitekey>
		<name>
			White Tablet
		</name>
		<desc>
			Ancient alien tablet with a bright white symbol.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			This device glows brightly with a lit white symbol resembling a mushroom.
			
			This tablet unlocks gates in an unknown location.
		</pda>
		<category>
			DownloadedData/Precursor/Scan
		</category>
	</whitekey>
	<SMDEPTH4><!-- do not remove, used for Website generation -->
		<name>
			Seamoth Depth Module Mk4
		</name>
		<desc>
			Raises depth limit to 1300m.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SMDEPTH4>
	<bioprocessor>
		<name>
			Bioprocessor
		</name>
		<desc>
			Decomposes and recombines organic matter into useful raw chemicals.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			This advanced machine is a key component of any main fabrication facility, and is capable of processing a multitude of biological materials into useful chemical products for use in more standard fabricator-based processes.
			
			In addition to several units of the base material, it requires some quantity of enzymatic reagents to facilitate the process, which will be gradually consumed over the duration of the production cycle. To conduct these reactions in a reasonable length of time - though note that for some reactions this can still be a subtantial duration - it will consume large quantities of power to maintain high temperatures and aggressive mechanical mixing.
			
			Efficiency can be increased in two ways:
			- Power consumption firmware upgrades, capable of reducing the power cost per production cycle (sold separately: not available in standard models)
			- Addition of a microbiotic component to increase yields for the same quantity of input ingredients
		</pda>
	</bioprocessor>
	<rebreathercharger>
		<name>
			Liquid Breathing Recharger
		</name>
		<desc>
			Refills liquid breathing systems in proximity.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			This pump will distribute fresh liquid breathing mix into any compatible equipped unit worn within the base, thanks to an advanced network of pipes embedded in the walls of the seabase. Features a large distribution tank which can be refilled at will.
		</pda>
	</rebreathercharger>
	<geyserfilter>
		<name>
			Geyser Particulate Filter
		</name>
		<desc>
			Collects certain trace minerals from volcanic activity.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			The geyser particulate filter uses a mesh of platinum-coated, electrically-charged wire to attract certain trace minerals present in the output of volcanic geysers, collecting them for use in fabrication. An essential component of plasteel production, this device - or conceptual analogues - has been a mainstay of deep-space outposts, be they scientific, military, or colony.
			
			Despite being ostensibly linked to a geyser, this device has no integrated thermoelectric conversion units, and so still requires a powered base nearby to draw power from.
		</pda>
	</geyserfilter>
	<enum>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</enum>
	<enum>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</enum>
	<enum>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</enum>
</Root>