<Root>
	<HoneycombComposite>
		<name>
			Honeycomb Composite Plating
		</name>
		<desc>
			A strong lightweight panel with extremely low thermal conductivity, and very effective force and vibration absorption capabilities.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</HoneycombComposite>
	<DenseAzurite>
		<name>
			Shaped Azurite
		</name>
		<desc>
			A more densely packed and energetically useful form of Azurite.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</DenseAzurite>
	<CrystalLens>
		<name>
			Refractive Lens
		</name>
		<desc>
			A lens with the ability to refract several kinds of energy and waves.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</CrystalLens>
	<HullPlating>
		<name>
			Hull Plating
		</name>
		<desc>
			Heavy armor for vehicles.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</HullPlating>
	<Sealant>
		<name>
			Sealant
		</name>
		<desc>
			A thick goo useful for impregnating other materials to induce impermeability.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Sealant>
	<SealFabric>
		<name>
			Sealed Fabric
		</name>
		<desc>
			Fabric woven together and thoroughly saturated with sealing compounds.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SealFabric>
	<Chlorine>
		<name>
			Chlorine
		</name>
		<desc>
			A highly poisonous gas which dissolves easily in water. Good for killing microorganisms.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Chlorine>
	<Luminol>
		<name>
			Luminol
		</name>
		<desc>
			A luminous fluid, colorless in small amounts and pale blue in large quantities.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Luminol>
	<SmartPolymer>
		<name>
			Smart Polymer
		</name>
		<desc>
			A flexible plastic material that remembers its original shape and returns to it when stress is released.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SmartPolymer>
	<WeakAcid>
		<name>
			Carboxylic Acid
		</name>
		<desc>
			A dilute organic acid, suitable for use in basic electronics.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</WeakAcid>
	<Motor>
		<name>
			Electric Motor
		</name>
		<desc>
			A midsize motor, capable of generating sufficient power to move sizeable machinery, pump fluids, or drive propulsion systems.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Motor>
	<BaseGlass>
		<name>
			Reinforced Glass
		</name>
		<desc>
			Laminated glass with titanium reinforcement, suitable for underwater pressure vessels.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</BaseGlass>
	<BioEnzymes>
		<name>
			Enzymes
		</name>
		<desc>
			Organic chemicals suitable for breaking down biological matter into simpler chemicals.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</BioEnzymes>
	<breathfluid>
		<name>
			Breathing Fluid
		</name>
		<desc>
			A nontoxic solvent saturated with oxygen, suitable for liquid-based respiration.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</breathfluid>
	<SealedSuit>
		<name>
			Electrochemical Suit
		</name>
		<desc>
			A suit made of molecularly impenetrable fabric.
			Stops almost all electrical and chemical penetration, but does little against radiation or thermal hazards.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SealedSuit>
	<RebreatherV2>
		<name>
			Liquid Breathing System
		</name>
		<desc>
			A breathing apparatus that uses an oxygen-saturated perfluorocarbon liquid instead of air.
			Allows for respiration at extreme depths and pressures without risk of barotrauma or toxicity from gas mixtures.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</RebreatherV2>
	<VENT_CRYSTAL>
		<name>
			Azurite
		</name>
		<desc>
			A luminous gemstone with exquisite optical properties and electromagnetic conductivity.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Found exclusively around certain thermal vents, these exotic crystals, despite having a similar gross molecular structure to common quartz, have electron distributions more commonly seen in metallic elements.
			
			This material can only form under very particular circumstances, specifically where superheated, mineral-rich water is injected into cold water, in the absence of dense flora which would absorb, or fast currents which would disperse the minerals before they can recrystallize. During this recrystallization process, many of the material's electrons are temporarily trapped within the crystal structure in a higher energy state.
			
			The light emitted by these deposits originates from those electrons the crystal structure dropping back into the ground state, releasing a photon in the process. While they remain energized, these electrons imbue the crystal structure with both high electrical and magnetic conductivity, allowing it to channel and reflect fields of the same.
			
			This arrangement also makes the crystal fairly unstable; Careless handling can result in violent fracturing, which destroys the aforementioned structure and releases a large quantity of energy.
		</pda>
		<header>
			azurite
		</header>
	</VENT_CRYSTAL>
	<PLATINUM>
		<name>
			Platinum
		</name>
		<desc>
			A dense, valuable, rare metal with extreme resistance to corrosion. In addition to being useful for creating alloys, it is also useful as a chemical catalyst with organic compounds.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Rarer and more valuable even than gold, platinum is a transition metal whose chief property is its extremely low chemical reactivity. This makes it all but impervious to corrosion, and allows it to mediate many chemical reactions without being consumed itself. In particular it is well-suited to rearranging the components of organic molecules.
			
			The extreme rarity of this metal can be partly attributed to its high density; during planetary formation and meteoric bombardment, it sinks to the core, leaving only traces in the crust. What little is left further settles to the lowest layers of the sediment, only becoming available via excavation or other disturbances to said sediment.
		</pda>
		<header>
			platinum
		</header>
	</PLATINUM>
	<PRESSURE_CRYSTALS>
		<name>
			Abyssoclase
		</name>
		<desc>
			Small, dense crystals formed under extreme pressure, with trace amounts of exotic elements such as Tellurium.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			In the deepest layers of the open ocean, where mineral-rich water expelled from thermal vents collects due to its greater density relative to ordinary seawater, the extreme pressure can force these minerals back out of solution.
			
			Abyssoclase is one such mineral, formed when a small seed crystal - possibly quartz, diamond, or sulfur - is coated with successive layers of silcia deposits rich in Tellurium and other rare elements.
			
			These deposits, due to the nature of the environment in which they form, are extremely dense, hard, and resistant to compressive forces. If integrated into another substrate, they can massively increase that material's mechanical strength.
		</pda>
		<header>
			voidspike
		</header>
	</PRESSURE_CRYSTALS>
	<PHASE_CRYSTAL>
		<name>
			Avolite
		</name>
		<desc>
			An integral part of ship drives and phase gates. These crystals are not fully understood, but are known to only form in deep space.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Avolite is an extremely rare crystal with extraordinary physical properties, the underlying mechanisms of which are very poorly understood, to the point where in eras past its properties would have been ascribed to theological origins and perhaps even formed the basis of primitive religions.
			
			This mineral demonstrates behavior analogous to the piezoelectric effect, except on a far larger scale, dragging spacetime itself as it warps when subjected to electromagnetic fields.
			
			This ability to manipulate space and time makes these crystals are an integral part of both interstellar propulsion systems and phase gates, and as a result Avolite is one of the most prized minerals in existence.
		</pda>
		<header>
			avolite
		</header>
	</PHASE_CRYSTAL>
	<IRIDIUM>
		<name>
			Iridium
		</name>
		<desc>
			An exotic and dense metal not typically found in most geologic strata.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			Iridium is not typically present in detectable quantities in planetary crusts, instead often only being found in meteorite deposits. High concentrations of this rare and dense metal are often indicators that the area is geologically linked with such an impactor.
		</pda>
		<header>
			iridium
		</header>
	</IRIDIUM>
	<ALKALI_PLANT>
		<name>
			Alkali Vines
		</name>
		<desc>
			A plant with alkaline gel filling its structure.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			This plant is fairly rare, found only in certain ecological niches with high mineral content and low exposure to light.
			
			The main body of the plant is comprised of a fibrous tube filled with a strongly alkaline gel. The primary purpose of this may be to deter creatures from eating the stems, or it may help the conduction of the plant's biochemical processes.
			
			Assessment: Inedible but possibly useful from a chemistry standpoint
		</pda>
	</ALKALI_PLANT>
	<VENT_KELP>
		<name>
			nameey
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</VENT_KELP>
	<SeamothVoidStealth>
		<name>
			Acoustic Suppression Module
		</name>
		<desc>
			Greatly reduces the detectability of basic seamoth systems to passive listeners.
			Will not affect active echolocators, or creatures at close range.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeamothVoidStealth>
	<t2battery>
		<name>
			Advanced Battery
		</name>
		<desc>
			A better battery, with significantly greater storage density. Its material construction precludes being adapted into a vehicular power cell.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</t2battery>
	<CyclopsHeat>
		<name>
			Cyclops Heat Dissipation Module
		</name>
		<desc>
			Provides the ability for the cyclops to shed excess heat in superheated environments, preventing serious overheating and fire.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</CyclopsHeat>
	<redkey>
		<name>
			Red Tablet
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			This device is dominated by an illuminated red symbol resembling an 'R'.
			
			Like other similar tablets, it presumably grants access to restricted spaces, with the special nature of this tablet - both its rarity and its seeming authority - probably indicating a similarly exclusive location, perhaps one only normally granting access to a select few.
		</pda>
		<category>
			DownloadedData/Precursor/Scan
		</category>
	</redkey>
	<whitekey>
		<name>
			White Tablet
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			This device glows brightly with a lit white symbol resembling a mushroom.
			
			This tablet unlocks gates in an unknown location.
		</pda>
		<category>
			DownloadedData/Precursor/Scan
		</category>
	</whitekey>
	<enum>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</enum>
</Root>