<Root>
  <voidpod>
	<name>
		Unknown Lifepod Crew Log
	</name>
	<pda>
		I can't tell whether I'm cursed or the luckiest guy alive. On one hand, my pod got me away from the Aurora long before any of the others did. On the other, all that accomplished was landing me all the way out here in the middle of open water. Nothing. As far as the scanner can see, aside from the area the wreck is sitting, this whole region is water that might as well be infinitely deep.
		
		Well, it briefly picked up some kind of isolated chunk of land off to the southwest, but its like a kilometer out, and the signal's crap. Given that the sonar says it's rated to a depth of 500 meters, it's gotta be pretty far down. I'll admit I'm kind of curious about what it is, but I'd be an idiot to leave the safety of this lifepod for some-
		
		[ghost leviathan screech]
		
		What the HELL is-
		
		[WHAM]
		
		No, it can't be. Not out here! Yeah, I heard those radio calls about sea monsters soon after the ship came down. But I've got nothing like that out here. There isn't even fish for ME to eat, let alone something that would want to eat me. No, that was probably just some debris falling out of orbit or some-
		
		[WHAM]
		
		[water noises]
		
		Great, now I've got to go out and patch the leak. At least I had the foresight to nick the repair tool from the cargo bay on the way to the lifepod, so that's gonna be easy. For once.
		
		[lifepod opening noise, another ghost leviathan screech]
	</pda>
	<category>
		DownloadedData/AuroraSurvivors
	</category>
	<audio>
		event:/player/story/VO/Ency_LifepodCrashZone1
	</audio>
  </voidpod>
  <voidspike>
	<name>
		Unknown Lifepod Crew Log #2
	</name>
	<pda>
		Well that settles it. I'm screwed.
		
		No sooner than I work out that I'm isolated but safe, some monster the size of a train comes out of nowhere and smashes my pod to pieces. I guess I should consider myself lucky that there was enough wreckage for me to pull myself out of the water, and avoid that...thing, so that it just got bored and left. That and the fact that I managed to collect most of my equipment from what was left of the storage locker.
		
		There might be enough residual charge left in the fabricator for me to be able to recycle some of the scrap; maybe I can make a seaglide and a couple of air tanks.
		
		After that? I have the option of swimming to the Aurora...and all the monsters that picked off the other crew. Or I could go towards that mystery area that might not even exist. And if there's nothing good down there, I won't even make it back to the surface. Or I could stay floating here for eternity as I watch an endless stream of ships get blown out of the sky trying to rescue the one that came before them.
		
		I've got lots of options, it's just that all of them suck!
	</pda>
	<category>
		DownloadedData/AuroraSurvivors
	</category>
	<audio>
		event:/player/story/VO/Ency_LifepodCrashZone2
	</audio>
  </voidspike>
  <treaderpod>
	<name>
		Lifepod 15 Crew Log
	</name>
	<pda>
		Ohhh, "it's only a small detour", they said. "There's probably nothing there", they said. That we'll just pop over, find nothing, and be on our merry way with nothing to show for it but a nice fat bonus from the Mongolian States. I had a bad feeling, of course, but nooooo, noone listens to me! Why would they? I've only been acting as a warp navigator for ten years!
		
		And now I'm stuck here AT THE BOTTOM OF THIS WORTHLESS OCEAN, in a lifepod whose floatation systems might as well say "NOT RATED FOR EXPOSURE TO WATER"! And that's not all! I've got a fabricator, medical cabinet, and radio, but guess what? NONE OF THEM WORK WITHOUT POWER! Of which there's precious little when you've got 400 meters of water over your solar panels.
		
		Damn Alterra and damn everything they make! Thanks to them, things could NOT get worse!
		
		[sudden loud treader thumping]
		
		Something's exploding up there. I guess it makes me feel a little better knowing that someone else is having just a bad a day as-
		
		[loud treader call]
		
		THE HELL WAS THAT?!
		
		[WHAM]
		
		[RUSHING WATER]		
	</pda>
	<category>
		DownloadedData/AuroraSurvivors
	</category>
	<audio>
		event:/player/story/VO/Ency_LifepodCrashZone2
	</audio>
  </treaderpod>
  <treadercave>
	<name>
		Lifepod 15 Crew Log #2
	</name>
	<pda>
		Word of advice: If ever you think things can't get worse, just remember - they can! I was trapped at the seafloor, but at least I had air, food, and was shielded from stuff that would want to eat me. Now my pod gets stomped flat by some ugly bastards with legs on their face! I barely had time to strap on my mask and air tank!
		
		I managed to scrounge up some metal to build a small habitat to give me somewhere to breathe and rest, but this isn't gonna last. I need food. I refuse to starve to death down here. So that's priority number one.
		
		Unfortunately, my little farm isn't doing so well. I don't get it; they said the melons needed lots of water to grow, but when I put them outside, they shrivelled up and died like they weren't literally SURROUNDED by water! At least I'm smart enough to know water when I feel it, so I'm good there. At least there's lots of fish to eat in the meantime.
		
		You know what else there's a ton of down here? Riches! Diamonds, rubies, gold, you name it, there's huge deposits of it. Shame I'll probably never get a chance to get rich with it, what with the being STUCK AT THE BOTTOM OF THE OCEAN and all.

		I think I see some rubies in the rocks in the ceiling, too. All I've gotta do is cut some of those vines loose.
	</pda>
	<category>
		DownloadedData/AuroraSurvivors
	</category>
	<audio>
		event:/player/story/VO/Ency_LifepodCrashZone2
	</audio>
  </treadercave>
  <crashmesa>
	<name>
		Lifepod 22 Crew Log
	</name>
	<pda>
		Roooooaaaaarrr!
	</pda>
	<category>
		DownloadedData/AuroraSurvivors
	</category>
	<audio>
		event:/player/story/VO/Ency_LifepodCrashZone2
	</audio>
  </crashmesa>
  <mountaincavehint>
	<name>
		Unknown lifepod transmission origin
	</name>
	<pda>
		A distress signal from an unknown lifepod contained no location data.
		
		Reported:
		-Lifepod sunk in a mountainous region with sparse vegetation
		-Modest depth at lifepod location, but much deeper water in all directions
		-Numerous small cave systems reported.
		-Origin far to the north of the Aurora
	</pda>
	<category>
		DownloadedData/Codes
	</category>
	<header>
	</header>
  </mountaincavehint>
  <mountainpod>
	<name>
		Mountain Lifepod Crew Log
	</name>
	<pda>
		So, imagine this. My pod detaches from the ship, comes down picture perfect. Lands upright, everything working as advertised. I'm gonna make it out of here! I just gotta stay put, ration my supplies a bit, and wait for rescue.
		
		That was three days ago. I'm starving, I'm tired, I have a bruise the size of a grapefruit, and I'm COMPLETELY fed up at this point. Turns out not everything was working right; my radio's picking up nothing but deep garbled nonsense about 'tracking subjects'. So I bet that nothing I send is making it out either.
		
		Guess that's it, then. Whatever is out there, I'm gonna just have to take my chances with it.
	</pda>
	<category>
		DownloadedData/AuroraSurvivors
	</category>
	<audio>
		event:/player/story/VO/Ency_LifepodCrashZone2
	</audio>
  </mountainpod>
  <mountaincave>
	<name>
		Mountain Cave Crew Log
	</name>
	<pda>
		Surviving out here has been...well, not EASY, but it hasn't been that hard, either. Food and water have been pretty trivial - though those squishy pink fish are getting rarer than I'd like - and there's lots of materials to be had. I even managed to grab some crates full of supplies and tools from the wreck up top.
		
		Unfortunately, there's a downside to this place; the whole region is crawling with sea monsters. One of em smashed my seamoth the moment I took it for a test drive. I made it out, but only barely.
		
		On the plus side, they tend to keep to the open areas, so I've so far been able to avoid them by holing up here in the cave, but I can't do that forever.
		
		Now, I'm not COMPLETELY out of ideas. I've got this blueprint for some kind of acoustic cloaking module maybe it'll help me evade detection from those things. To make it, though, I'll need a lot of exotic refractory crystals. The good news? This biome is littered with some that'll work just fine; I found three in this room alone. Bad news? Three's not enough...I need more like THIRTY. Soooo...sooner or later I'm gonna have to risk it and go outside to look for more.
		
		God, if this works, I can make a new seamoth, and slip right past these blasted giants and head to the Aurora to wait for rescue. If it doesn't.......
	</pda>
	<category>
		DownloadedData/AuroraSurvivors
	</category>
	<audio>
		event:/player/story/VO/Ency_LifepodCrashZone2
	</audio>
  </mountaincave>
  <bloodtrench>
	<name>
		Lifepod 18 Crew Log
	</name>
	<pda>
		Oh, god, oh god, oh god, this can't be happening! I can't be getting stranded on some godforsaken planet out on the edge of Federation space!
		
		[Metal banging]
		
		OK, OK, it's definitely happening! I really am about to crash into an alien ocean!
		
		[splashdown]
		
		And I'm in water, great. Well, I guess mom wasn't kidding when she said swimming lessons could end up saving my life.
		
		[Hiss, followed by bubbling sound]
		
		...Or they WOULD, if not for the fact that I'm sinking to the bottom.
		
		[thud]
		
		Can I even make it to the surface from here? Sigh.
		
		Okay, this isn't actually that bad. Yeah, the grass is blood-red, but it's clear, bright and sandy so it's not like I'm in the depths. Maybe I'm even near shore. No problem, I'll get out of this. Just keep calm. Everything's gonna be JUST fine.
		
		[bone shark noise, then thud]
		
		[second of silence]
		
		[metal groaning and metal-on-dirt noises]
		
		I'm sinking again?! You have GOT to be kidding me!
		
		[pause, then thud]
		
		Oh, it's really dark down here. Like pitch black...aside from those terrifying looking plants over there. 
		
		Wait, what's that that light over there? It's moving...closer...GAAAH!
		
		[zapping sound]
	</pda>
	<category>
		DownloadedData/AuroraSurvivors
	</category>
	<audio>
		event:/player/story/VO/Ency_LifepodCrashZone2
	</audio>
  </bloodtrench>
</Root>