<Root>
  <DEGASI1>
    <name>
		Underwater Degasi Base
	</name>
    <desc>

	</desc>
   	 <pda>

	</pda>
    <databox>

	</databox>
    <water>

	</water>
    	<breathcharge>
		Fragments of a machine to recharge liquid breathing systems
	</breathcharge>
    	<azurite>

	</azurite>
  </DEGASI1>
  <JELLYSHROOM>
    	<name>
		Jellyshroom Caves
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<mushroom>

	</mushroom>
    	<magnetite>

	</magnetite>
    	<degasi>
		The decaying remains of a seabase, once inhabited by the survivors of the Degasi
	</degasi>
  </JELLYSHROOM>
  <POD3>
    	<name>
		Northern Kelp Forest
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<databox>
		A databox containing the blueprint for a compass
	</databox>
    	<geyser>
		A cave south of lifepod 3 containing an undersea geyser, several broken Nanolathing Drones, and extremely high numbers of both Crashfish and Drooping Stingers
	</geyser>
  </POD3>
  <POD19>
    	<name>
		Officer Keen's Lifepod
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<databox>

	</databox>
    	<cache>

	</cache>
  </POD19>
  <POD17>
    	<name>
		Western Grassy Plateaus
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<seamoth>

	</seamoth>
    	<terminal>

	</terminal>
    	<jelly>

	</jelly>
    	<room>

	</room>
  </POD17>
  <POD6>
    	<name>
		Eastern Grassy Plateaus
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<seacrown>
		A rare specimen of alien flora, remarkable for its internal bacterial colonies
	</seacrown>
    	<salve>
		A species of red flora, the leaves of which are coated in oils that have medicinal properties
	</salve>
  </POD6>
  <KOOSH>
    	<name>
		Bulb Zone
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<mushkoosh>
		A cave connecting the Mushroom Forest and Bulb Zone, and home to a unique species of chemosynthetic coral. 
	</mushkoosh>
    	<mercury>
		Geologically active caves containing cinnabar ore
	</mercury>
    	<reinf>
		A databox containing the blueprint for a Reinforced Dive Suit
	</reinf>
  </KOOSH>
  <DUNECENTRAL>
    	<name>
		The Dunes
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<reaper>
		
	</reaper>
    	<shroom>
		Blue mushroom-like plants that emit light-sensitive seed pods
	</shroom>
    	<azurite>
		Abundant deposits of the volatile mineral Azurite
	</azurite>
    	<suit>
		A databox for the Electrochemical Suit
	</suit>
  </DUNECENTRAL>
  <METEOR>
    	<name>
		Dunes Meteor
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<meteor>
		The core of a large meteorite, comprised of several useful metals
	</meteor>
    	<cache>
		An alien structure containing a number of Ion Cubes, and what seem to be the memories of an alien lifeform
	</cache>
  </METEOR>
  <UNDERISLANDS>
    	<name>
		Underwater Islands
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<piezo>
		Strange, buoyant crystals that will occasionally emit disruptive electromagnetic blasts that disrupt nearby electrical systems.
	</piezo>
    	<wreck>
A large wreck from the aurora, a piece of which broke off and fell into the depths before it could be explored
	</wreck>
    	<farmer>
		A databox containing the blueprints for an automated harvesting device
	</farmer>
    	<databox>
		A databox containing the blueprint for an integrated fire suppression module for large submersibles
	</databox>
    	<room>
		A room containing a number of databoxes, originally blocked by a dislodged titanium door 
	</room>
  </UNDERISLANDS>
  <BKELPTRENCH>
    	<name>
		Blood Kelp Trench
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<pod1>

	</pod1>
    	<chit>

	</chit>
    	<databox>

	</databox>
  </BKELPTRENCH>
  <NBKELP>
    	<name>
		Northern Blood Kelp
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<pod2>

	</pod2>
    	<cache>

	</cache>
    		<levi>

	</levi>
  </NBKELP>
  <BONEFIELD>
    	<name>
		Bones Field
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<skull>
		An extremely large skull and upper ribcage of an ancient creature dwarfing anything encountered on the planet
	</skull>
    	<sulfur>
		Large deposits of pure, crystalline sulfur
	</sulfur>
    	<seal>
		A damaged seamoth upgrade for reducing power leakage to the environment
	</seal>
    	<levi>
		A young and aggressive Ghost Leviathan
	</levi>
  </BONEFIELD>
  <DRF>
    	<name>
		Disease Research Facility
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<terminal1>
		A download of alien biological and paleontological data, pertaining to various species on 4546b, both extant and extinct
	</terminal1>
    	<damage>
		A download of alien black box data, detailing how the facility was destroyed through the actions of an enraged Sea Dragon 
	</damage>
    	<tablet>
		A broken, flickering white tablet, similar to other previously encountered tablets, inside the skeleton of a large research specimen
	</tablet>
    	<cycheat>
		A download of alien technological data that has been adapted into a heat rejection upgrade for the Cyclops
	</cycheat>
    	<disease>
		A download of alien historical data pertaining to the nature and origins of the “Kharaa” bacterium
	</disease>
    	<egg>
		The preserved egg of a Sea Dragon Leviathan
	</egg>
    	<dragon>
		The skeleton of a Sea Dragon Leviathan. Many bones appear to have been fractured or broken in a high velocity impact
	</dragon>
    	<warper>
		Various body parts belonging to Warpers 
	</warper>
  </DRF>
  <LAVACASTLE>
    	<name>
		Lava Castle
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<kyanite>
		Collectible kyanite crystals, formed via high levels of volcanic activity
	</kyanite>
    	<tablet>
		A pristine, sky-blue tablet, certain to be similar in function to other alien tablets
	</tablet>
    	<ion>
		A download of alien technological data, adapted into blueprints for ion cube-based batteries
	</ion>
    	<tap>
		A download of alien structural data, indicating how to tap into the energy running through alien structures
	</tap>
  </LAVACASTLE>
  <CRAG>
    	<name>
		Crag Field
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<pod7>
		The remains of Lifepod 7. Its fabricator appears to have malfunctioned during evacuation
	</pod7>
    	<scoop>
		A databox containing the blueprint for a phytoplankton collection module
	</scoop>
  </CRAG>
  <FLOATISLAND>
    	<name>
		Floating Island
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<degasi>
		(not sure what should go here)
	</degasi>
    	<keen>
		The last known location of First Officer Keen, and a pda detailing his encounter with Yu, the only other Aurora survivor who appeared to survive for any length of time
</keen>
    	<arch>
		A strange alien arch hidden within a cave
	</arch>
  </FLOATISLAND>
  <MOUNTAINISLAND>
    	<name>
		Mountain Island
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<gun>

	</gun>
    	<beachpda>

	</beachpda>
    	<cavepda>

	</cavepda>
    	<arch>
		An alien teleporter, leading to a corresponding structure in a cave on a floating island
	</arch>
    	<battery>
		A damaged, malfunctioning battery made from Azurite-based materials
	</battery>
    	<tablet>
		A shattered, red tablet of non-human design. 
	</tablet>
  </MOUNTAINISLAND>
  <GUN>
    	<name>
		Quarantine Enforcement Platform
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<cube>
		Glowing green cubes containing immense ionic energy
	</cube>
    	<denied>
		A strange alien terminal, the attempted usage of which was denied for reasons of infection, and revealed the true purpose of the containing structure 
	</denied>
    	<jailbreak>
		A download of what appears to be alien malware, making the laser cutter capable of stripping salvage from the hull of the aurora.

&lt;b&gt;Reminder from Alterra: Salvage of the Aurora is illegal under intergalactic law&lt;/b&gt;
	</jailbreak>
  </GUN>
  <FLOATDEGASI>
    	<name>
		Island Degasi Wrecks
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<main>

	</main>
    	<outside>

	</outside>
    	<return>

	</return>
    	<init>

	</init>
  </FLOATDEGASI>
  <DUNEARCH>
    	<name>
		Dunes Arch
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<reaper>

	</reaper>
    	<bioproc>
		Fragments of a bioprocessor machine
	</bioproc>
    	<liqbr>
		A databox containing the blueprints for a liquid breathing system
	</liqbr>
  </DUNEARCH>
  <GRANDREEF>
    	<name>
		Grand Reef
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<platinum>
		Elemental platinum, unearthed by the titanic footsteps of the Sea Treaders
	</platinum>
    	<bioproc>
		Fragments of a bioprocessor machine
	</bioproc>
    	<poo>
The waste products of Sea Treaders, which may serve as useful biochemical feedstock into various processes
	</poo>
    	<sealed>
		A databox containing the blueprint for watertight, electrically insulative fabric
	</sealed>
    	<levi>

	</levi>
  </GRANDREEF>
  <MUSHTREE>
    	<name>
		Mushroom Tree
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<initpda>
		The log of an Aurora survivor, designated to rescue aurora passenger Jochi Khasar or document their fate if this proved impossible
	</initpda>
    	<treepda>
		The last words of an Aurora survivor who became trapped in the hollowed caverns of a large coral tree
	</treepda>
    	<chit>
		An installable overclock for the Laser Cutter, allowing it to carve through reinforced bulkheads
	</chit>
    	<bacteria>
		Large colonies of bacteria, containing enzymes capable of breaking down biological matter
	</bacteria>
  </MUSHTREE>
  <MOUNTAINPOD>
    	<name>
		Lifepod 14
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<podpda>

	</podpda>
    	<podpda2>

	</podpda2>
    	<basepda>

	</basepda>
    	<mask>
		A damaged databox containing the blueprint for a recirculation mask, wedged into a metal grille
	</mask>
    	<stealth>
		A databox containing the blueprints for an experimental noise suppression module, intended to enable evading detection by Reaper Leviathans
	</stealth>
    	<knife>
		A survival knife, upgraded to sear whatever it comes into contact with
	</knife>
    	<battery>

	</battery>
  </MOUNTAINPOD>
  <TREADERPOD>
    	<name>
		Lifepod 9
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<treader>

	</treader>
    	<platinum>
		Elemental platinum, unearthed by the titanic footsteps of the Sea Treaders.
	</platinum>
    	<enzy>

	</enzy>
    	<basepda>

	</basepda>
    	<databox>

	</databox>
  </TREADERPOD>
  <GLASSFOREST>
    	<name>
		Glass Forest
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<databox>

	</databox>
    	<bioproc>

	</bioproc>
    	<deepvine>

	</deepvine>
    	<levi>

	</levi>
  </GLASSFOREST>
  <CRASH>
    	<name>
		Crash Zone
	</name>
    	<desc>

	</desc>
    	<pda>

	</pda>
    	<pod4>

	</pod4>
    	<crashmesa>

	</crashmesa>
    	<reaper>

	</reaper>
    	<sanctuary>

	</sanctuary>
    	<trailerbase>

	</trailerbase>
    	<rebreather>

	</rebreather>
  </CRASH>
  <DEGASIEND>
	<name>
		Deep Degasi Base
	</name>
	<desc>
		
	</desc>
	<pda>
		
	</pda>
	<end>
		A recording of the demise of the Degasi survivors as a result of Marguerit Maida bringing an injured leviathan, attracting another which attacked the base.
	</end>
	<tablet>
		A broken orange tablet in the same general design of the purple variant, with unknown usage.
	</tablet>
	<rebreather>
		The final fragments to create a construction blueprint for a machine to recharge liquid breathing systems.
	</rebreather>
  </DEGASIEND>
  <VOID>
	<name>
		Crater Edge
	</name>
	<desc>
		
	</desc>
	<pda>
		
	</pda>
	<destroy>
		Audio of the final moments of lifepod 15 as it was destroyed by a ghost leviathan.
	</destroy>
	<end>
		A log from the occupant of lifepod 15 as they examined their limited options and discussed visiting an unknown deep region further away from the main crater.
	</end>
	<databox>
		A databox containing the blueprint for tough metal plating to build advanced vehicles.
	</databox>
	<items>
		Strange crystals formed under extreme pressure, with commensurate fabrication applications.
	</items>
	<levi>
		A large aggressive creature that makes use of light and electricity based attacks.
	</levi>
  </VOID>
</Root>